<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>@ Music on Andre Afonso</title>
    <link>/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in @ Music on Andre Afonso</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Church Music</title>
      <link>/music/church-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/church-music/</guid>
      <description>Here are some of the musics I already played in the church context.
Só a Ti </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music Sheets</title>
      <link>/music/music-sheets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/music-sheets/</guid>
      <description>The purpose of this page is to track my progress regarding music sheet reading capabilities and what instruments I play the most.
Tracker    Title Type Instrument Practiced Rehearsed Where Played Live     Guardians of Liberty March Bass Drum Yes Yes Orchestra No   Life and Peace March Drum Set No No  No   New Castle March March Drum Set No No  No   Whispers in the Wind March Glock Yes No  No   Just Dance Song Drum Set Yes Yes Orchestra No   Counting Stars Song Drum Set Yes No  No   Shut Up and Dance Song Drum Set Yes No  No   Bom Rapaz Song Drum Set Yes Yes Orchestra No   Sentir o Sol Song Drum Set + Shaker Yes Yes Orchestra No   Saia da Carolina Song Drum Set Yes Yes Orchestra No   Smoke on the water Song Drum Set No No  No   Mission:Impossible Theme Drum Set Yes Yes Orchestra No    Produced  Welcome to the Black Parade Welcome to the Black Parade  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My music learning path</title>
      <link>/music/learning-path/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 16:48:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/learning-path/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always liked music!
Can&amp;rsquo;t remember when it all started but my path took wings when my parents got me a cheap guitar and I just spent my time trying things&amp;hellip; not as hard as I would like nowadays but hey&amp;hellip; we can&amp;rsquo;t all be Jacobs right? :p
Path  2004 - Self learned acoustic guitar 2004 - Played in the boy scouts and in catholic church 2008 - Joined a university band called anTUNiA as guitarist and percussionist  https://www.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
